Satsang with Mooji
Thank you.
Let's go.
If,
perchance, I hadn't taken
Jonathan Joestar's body,
I could not have survived
for 100 long years.
However, this body seems to be
linked to Jonathan's descendants.
What is it that concerns you?
Lord Dio.
Jonathan Joestar's bloodline.
They suspect my existence.
And this new power I acquired
from having Jonathan's body.
The stand.
But this stand of mine, it appears to
affect the bodies of his descendants.
Strength and weakness are simply
two sides of the same coin.
In any case, Lord Dio,
please feel reassured.
I've already taken the necessary actions.
Hey! Holly!
Holly!
Holly! Holly! Holly?
Hmm?
Holly, what's wrong?
Papa?
Nothing's wrong, Papa.
I just need to catch up on my sleep.
Are you absolutely certain
that you're all right?
No, no, I'm fine, Papa.
You simply worry too much.
Hmm.
Do I?
Well, that boy Jotaro made
us all worry too much.
You should go rest up.
No, silly papa.
What do you need? What?
Oh, yes.
I was wondering if we'd receive some
reply from the Speedwagon Foundation.
But I don't know where the fax machine is.
Oh, the fax is in the room
across from the kitchen.
If something comes in,
I'll bring it to you later.
Hmm.
Right then.
By the way, where's Jotaro?
At school, of course.
Hey, Jojo, how come you
didn't come to school?
It's been four days.
Hey, you, stop trying to rub
those against Jojo's arm.
You got a problem, ugly?
Shut up, flat chest.
Ugly.
I don't want your flat chest telling
me that, either, you flat chest!
Jojo!
Jojo? Huh?
What's wrong?
Choo-choo!
a cut on my knee what's going on did i get
cut by that branch no that's not it it was
cut before i fell that's why i lost my
footing on the steps it
can't be a where is he
I'm sure he came this way.
Choo-choo!
Where did he go?
Oh, good.
I finally found you.
I said to myself, he's hurt, so I
went back to get a bandage for you.
Ah, here you are.
Please, use this.
Oh.
Thanks.
What the hell is going on?
This is no girl's strength.
That's right.
That girl has been possessed by my stand.
By your stand?
Just who the hell are you?
Noriyaki Kakyoin.
And my stand's name is Hierophant Green.
Earlier, I pledged my loyalty to Lord Dio.
Dio?
What?
What is that thing?
By the way, attacking my stand will
end up injuring that girl. Understand?
She really seems to care a lot about you.
Now that it's been dragged out,
I can see it's the kind of stand
that has to possess someone.
Don't pretend to be tough.
I can see those grip marks.
Let me choke you just a little bit more.
And then when you pass out, I'll
drag your ass home to the old man.
There, you can talk all you want.
About Dio.
You dragged out my stand.
Now you're going to regret that.
Oh, you actually managed to put your
guard up before Hierophant could strike.
My stand hates to be in open spaces, so
he always tends to lurk behind something.
Naturally, if you drag
him out, he'll get angry.
Didn't I tell you that I would make you
regret that you dragged out my stand?
Don't think you've seen
everything Hierophant can do.
What do you mean?
Die!
Emerald Splash!
Those things that look like
the bodily fluids of my
hierophant green are actually
visions of destructive energy,
sacrificing yourself to protect a woman.
How foolish you are.
What do you think you
can do with that body?
You're just like a sandbag before a boxer.
It seems you stand up only
to be beaten down again.
Pretty much everyone's written
me off as a delinquent.
So I'm always beating up
guys who challenge me.
And handing out lessons to those stuck-up
morons that call themselves teachers.
But even I...
can sense the disgusting evil in you.
Evil? What?
An evil person is a coward
who would take advantage
of the weak and use them
to fight his battles.
Are you talking about
that woman over there?
Ha!
Let the Vanquished be the evil,
and the victor be the just.
How you get there doesn't matter.
The Vanquished is the evil?
Enough of this talk.
Now, Emerald Splash!
If the Vanquished is the evil...
Hurrah!
Well then, no doubt.
You are the evil one.
Mayor!
What a powerful stand.
It's…
Where am I?
What a pain.
Not good.
He won't make it.
What are you talking about?
Chotaro, this is no fault of yours.
As for the reason why
this young man pledged
his loyalty to Dio and then attacked you,
That reason is right here.
What the hell is that?
That thing is a bud of flesh
created from Dio's cells.
A bud of flesh?
You see, approximately four
months ago, in Cairo, Egypt,
I too was approached by Dio.
My occupation is fortune-telling.
I had a shop in Cairo, Egypt.
On my way home from the shop one evening,
he suddenly appeared in front of me,
his icy gaze creeping into my heart.
Hair of spun gold.
Translucent white skin.
I'd already heard about him from Mr.
Joestar So I immediately
recognized him as Dio.
You there!
I've heard you possess an ability
that ordinary people don't have.
I would be extremely pleased if you
would be so kind as to show it to me!
It was then I felt the fear.
The words he spoke were somehow
relaxing and were dangerously sweet,
and therefore even more terrifying.
I ran with no thought of fighting him.
Otherwise,
a bud of flesh would have
been implanted in me,
And just like this unfortunate young man,
I would have pledged my
absolute loyalty to Dio.
In the end, my brain would have been consumed
in a few years and I would have died.
Just a minute.
Kakyoin isn't dead yet.
Wait, Jotaro!
That thing will attack and infiltrate the
brain of anyone who tries to remove it!
Just stay away.
I'll pull this sucker out
without damaging his brain.
Don't! Don't go!
Damn you!
D... Dio...
Jotaro, are you alright?
Jotaro!
you but why don't move if i don't
get this just right you're dead meat
Jotaro, this is too dangerous.
Just a moment, Avdol.
Let's wait and have faith in my grandson.
Look, neither Jotaro nor
his stand tremble one bit.
More precisely than a machine.
More powerfully, he is
slowly working it loose.
That's it!
Johtaro!
Magician's Red!
Why did you risk your own life to help me?
Well, good question.
Wish I knew that myself.
What's that?
It's from the kitchen.
Oh, no!
Holly!
Miss Holly!
Holly! Holly! Holly!
Hang on, Holly!
Holly!
Mr.
Joestar, is it?
The one thing that I feared
most has finally come to pass.
Jotaro.
Hey, what do you mean by that?
I thought it was strange
that because of Dio,
stand abilities had
appeared in Jotaro and me.
But nothing had happened to Holly.
Basically,
a stand is called forth by
a user's spiritual strength
and pressed into action by
their fighting instincts.
But Miss Holly has a
quiet and gentle nature
that is not well suited
to controlling a stand.
No, even worse than that,
it's actually done her harm.
We've worried that she did
not have the power to resist.
Worried that she didn't have
the power to battle Dio's spell.
In the past,
I've known people who died because of
the damage caused by their own stands.
However, in the case of Miss Holly,
I believe that there is still hope.
What do we do?
There's only one way.
Defeat Dio and break this cursed spell.
That is true, but where is Dio right now?
We do not even have a clue
about where to search.
Nile, Tzitzi, inhabits the
Nile River regions of Egypt?
Specifically,
the one with a striped pattern on its
legs is called the Aswan Tzitzi Fly!
This is a fax from someplace
called the Speed Wagon Foundation.
Which means that he's still in!
In Egypt, all along he was still in Egypt?
and in the Aswan region.
Three months ago, my family
and I were traveling in Egypt,
and that was where and when I met Dio.
Dio's existence terrified me,
and I succumbed to his attack.
Never again will I allow myself
to go through that misery.
Jotaro, I'm going to Egypt too.
But why? Why you?
Well, that's a good question.
I wish I knew why myself.
You helped me return to my senses.
That's reason enough.
Holly, I promise I'll save you.
I promise I'll save you.
We'll never know when the
enemy might attack us.
So to avoid involving
innocent people in this.
We'll be going aboard the
Speedwagon Foundation's private jet.
Jotaro
Before we leave, please allow me
to give your stand a proper name.
Here, from this tarot deck,
choose any one card that you like.
The Star card.
I will name it.
Your stand shall be called Star Platinum.
What this card implies will be revealed.
Through the journey we are about to begin?
All right, let's go there.
Well now, they figured it
out, my current location.
They're coming to Egypt.
Thank you.